tamilrockers.website 2016-06-21

# Privacy Policy » friendsQ-Indian Social Network

**WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS**

At friendsQ we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

This policy covers how friendsQ treats personal information that friendsQ collects and receives, including information related to your past use of friendsQ products and services. Personal information is information about an identifiable individual like your name, email address or phone number and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This privacy policy only applies to friendsQ. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that friendsQ does not own or control, such as friendsQ-enhanced applications and websites or to people that friendsQ does not employ or manage. 

_By using or accessing friendsQ, you agree to our privacy policy outlined on this page._

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**     
**  
**

**  

  1. 1.Children

**No information from children under age 13.**  If you are under age 13, please do not attempt to register for friendsQ or provide any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under age 13, please contact us at [friendsq.com@gmail.com](mailto:friendsq.com@gmail.com?Subject=UnderAge%20Member)

**Parental participation.**  We strongly recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet and we encourage parents to teach their children about safe internet use practices. Materials to help parents talk to their children about safe internet use can be found [here.](http://www.fosi.org/)

****  

  2. 2.Information We Receive
  
**   
  
**  

    * ● Information you provide to us :
  
**   

**Personal information.**  When you sign up for friendsQ you provide us with your name, email, gender, and birth date. During the registration process we give you the opportunity to provide additional profile information, such as where you went to school and where you work, and to add a picture of yourself, to help your friends connect with you. In some cases we may ask for additional information for security reasons or to provide specific services to you. Once you register you can visit your profile at any time to add or remove personal information about yourself. You can add basic information about yourself, such as information about your hometown, family, relationships, and your political and religious views. You can also add other information about yourself including your activities, interests, contact information, as well as more information about your education and job history. 

**Content.**  One of the primary reasons people use friendsQ is to share content with others. Examples include when you update your status, upload or take a photo, upload or record a video, share a link, create an event or a group, make a comment, write something on someone’s Wall, write a note, or send someone a message. If you do not want us to store metadata associated with content you share on friendsQ (such as photos, videos, music), please remove the metadata before uploading the content. 

**Transactional Information.**  We may retain the details of transactions or payments you make on friendsQ. However, we will only keep your payment source account number with your consent. 

**Friend Information.**  We offer contact importer tools to help you upload your friends’ addresses so that you can find your friends on friendsQ, and invite your contacts who do not have friendsQ accounts to join. If you give us your password to retrieve those contacts, we will not store your password after you have uploaded your contacts’ information. 

**Location Information.**  When you share your location with others or add a location to something you post, we treat that like any other content you post (for example, it is subject to your [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/)). If we offer a service that supports this type of location sharing we will present you with an opt-in choice of whether you want to participate.    
**  
**

**  
****  

    * ● Information we collect when you interact with friendsQ :
  
**   

******Site activity information.**  We keep track of the actions you take on friendsQ, such as adding a friend, becoming a fan of a friendsQ Page, joining a group or an event, creating a photo album, sending a gift, poking another user, indicating you “like” a post, attending an event, buying or selling a product, payment transaction history or authorizing an application. In some cases you are also taking an action when you provide information or content to us. For example, if you share a photo, video or music in addition to storing the actual content you uploaded, we might log the fact you shared it. 

**Access Device and Browser Information.**  When you access friendsQ from a computer, mobile phone or any other device, we may collect information from that device about your browser type, location, and IP address, as well as the pages you visit. 

**  
Cookie Information.** We use "cookies" (small pieces of data we store for an extended period of time on your computer, mobile phone, or any other device) to make friendsQ easier to use, to make our advertising better, and to protect both you and friendsQ. For example, we use them to store your login ID (but never your password) to make it easier for you to login whenever you come back to friendsQ. We also use them to confirm that you are logged into friendsQ, and to know when you are interacting with friendsQ applications and websites, our widgets and Share buttons, and our advertisements. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases that may impact your ability to use friendsQ.    
**  
**

**  
****  

    * ● Information we receive from third parties :
  
**   

******friendsQ Application Platform and friendsQ Like.**  We do not own or operate the applications that you use through friendsQ Application Platform (such as games and utilities) or the websites that you interact with through friendsQ Like. We refer to them as “friendsQ-enhanced” applications and websites because they use our Platform to provide you with social features. Whenever you authorize a friendsQ-enhanced application or website, we will receive information from them, including information about actions you take. In some cases, in order to personalize the process of connecting, we may receive a limited amount of information even before you authorize the application or website. 

**Information from other websites.**  We may institute programs with advertising partners and other websites in which they share information with us : 

      * ● We may ask advertisers to tell us how our users responded to the ads we showed them (and for comparison purposes, how other users who didn’t see the ads acted on their site). This data sharing, commonly known as “conversion tracking,” helps us measure our advertising effectiveness and improve the quality of the advertisements you see. 

      * ● We may receive information about whether or not you’ve seen or interacted with certain ads on other sites in order to measure the effectiveness of those ads.

If in any of these cases we receive data that we do not already have, we will “anonymize” it within 180 days, meaning we will stop associating the information with any particular user. If we institute these programs, we will only use the information in the ways we explain in the “How We Use Your Information” section below. 

**Information from other users.**  We may collect information about you from other friendsQ users, such as when you buy or sell a product from another user, a friend tags you in a photo or video, provides friend details, or indicates a relationship with you. You can limit this from your [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/). 

**  

  3. 3\. Information You Share With Third Parties
  
**   

**** We take steps to ensure that others use information that you share on friendsQ in a manner consistent with your [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/), but we cannot guarantee that they will follow our rules. Read the following section to learn more about how you can protect yourself when you share information with third parties. 

**Sharing information on friendsQ.**  We designed our [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/) to enable you to control how you share your information on friendsQ. You should review the default [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/) to make sure they reflect your preferences. Here are some specific things to remember : 

    * ● You can control the visibility of most of the information you share on friendsQ through the [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/) you select. 

    * ● Certain categories of information such as your name, profile photo, list of friends and pages you are a fan of, gender, and networks you belong to are considered publicly available, and therefore do not have privacy settings. You can limit the ability of others to find this information on third party search engines through your search [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/). 

    * ● Some of the content you share and the actions you take will show up on your friends’ home pages and other pages they visit. 

    * ● Even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/), or it was copied or stored by other users. 

    * ● You understand that information might be re-shared or copied by other users. 

    * ● Certain types of communications that you send to other users cannot be removed, such as messages. 

    * ● When you post information on another user’s profile or comment on another user’s post, that information will be subject to the other user’s [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/). 

    * ● If you use an external source to publish information to friendsQ (such as a mobile application or a Connect or Like site), you should check the privacy setting for that post, as it is set by that external source.

**“Everyone” Privacy Setting.**  Information set to “everyone” is publicly available information, may be accessed by everyone on the Internet (including people not logged into friendsQ), is subject to indexing by third party search engines, may be associated with you outside of friendsQ (such as when you visit other sites on the internet), and may be imported and exported by us and others without privacy limitations. The default privacy setting for certain types of information you post on friendsQ is set to “everyone.” You can review and change the default settings in your [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/). If you delete “everyone” content that you posted on friendsQ, we will remove it from your friendsQ profile, but have no control over its use outside of friendsQ.  **

friendsQ Application Platform.

**  As mentioned above, we do not own or operate friendsQ-enhanced applications or websites. That means that when you visit friendsQ-enhanced applications and websites you are making your friendsQ information available to someone other than friendsQ. To help those applications and sites operate, they receive publicly available information automatically when you visit them, and additional information when you formally authorize or connect your friendsQ account with them.
    * ● We may make information about the location of your computer or access device and your age available to friendsQ–enhanced applications and websites in order to help them implement appropriate security measures and control the distribution of age-appropriate content.

You should always review the policies of third party applications and websites to make sure you are comfortable with the ways in which they use information you share with them. We do not guarantee that they will follow our rules.  **

Exporting Information.

**  You (and those you make your information available to) may use tools like RSS feeds, mobile phone address books, or copy and paste functions, to capture and export information from friendsQ, including your information and information about you. 

**Advertisements.**  Sometimes the advertisers who present ads on friendsQ use technological methods to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. You may also use your browser cookie settings to limit or prevent the placement of cookies by advertising networks. 

**Links.**  When you click on links on friendsQ you may leave our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites, and we encourage you to read their privacy statements.

**  

  4. 4\. How We Use Your Information
  
**

**** We use the information we collect to try to provide a safe, efficient, and customized experience. Here are some of the details on how we do that : 

**To manage the service.**  We use the information we collect to provide our services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features, and to provide you with customer support. We use the information to prevent potentially illegal activities, and to enforce our [Statement of Rights and Responsibilities](http://friendsq.com/terms/). For example, we ask for your date of birth to verify that you are over age 13 and so that we can better limit your access to content and advertisements that are not age appropriate. We also use a variety of technological systems to detect and address anomalous activity and screen content to prevent abuse such as spam. These efforts may on occasion result in a temporary or permanent suspension or termination of some functions for some users. 

**To contact you.**  We may contact you with service-related announcements from time to time. You may opt out of all communications except essential updates on your [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/). We may include content you see on friendsQ in the emails we send to you. 

**To serve personalized advertising to you.**  We don’t share your information with advertisers without your consent. (An example of consent would be if you asked us to provide your shipping address to an advertiser to receive a free sample.) We allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements and we may use any of the non-personally identifiable attributes we have collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. For example, we might use your interest in football to show you ads for football equipment, but we do not tell the football equipment company who you are. Even though we do not share your information with advertisers without your consent, when you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement there is a possibility that the advertiser may place a cookie in your browser and note that it meets the criteria they selected. 

**To serve social ads**. We occasionally pair advertisements we serve with relevant information we have about you and your friends to make advertisements more interesting and more tailored to you and your friends. For example, if you become a fan of a Page, we may display your name and profile photo next to an advertisement for that Page that is displayed to your friends. We only share the personally identifiable information visible in the social ad with the friend who can see the ad. 

**To supplement your profile.**  We may use information about you that we collect from other friendsQ users to supplement your profile (such as when you are tagged in a photo or mentioned in a status update). In such cases we generally allow you to direct how that information is shared in your [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/) or give you the ability to remove the content (such as allowing you to remove a photo tag of you) or limit its visibility on friendsQ. 

**To make Suggestions.**  We use your profile information, the addresses you import through our contact importers, and other relevant information, to help you connect with your friends, including making suggestions to you and other users that you connect with on friendsQ. If you want to limit your visibility in suggestions we make to other people, you can adjust your search visibility[privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/), as you will only be visible in our suggestions to the extent you choose to be visible in public search listings. You may also block specific individual users from being suggested to you and you from being suggested to them. 

**Downloadable Software.**  Certain downloadable software applications and applets that we offer, such as our browser toolbars photo, video and music uploaders, transmit data to us. We may not make a formal disclosure if we believe our collection of and use of the information is the obvious purpose of the application, such as the fact that we receive photos, videos and music when you use our photo, video and music uploader. 

**Memorializing Accounts.**  If we are [notified](mailto:friendsq.com@gmail.com?Subject=Memorialize%20Account) that a user is deceased, we may memorialize the user’s account. In such cases we restrict profile access to confirmed friends, and allow friends and family to write on the user’s Wall in remembrance. We may close an account if we receive a formal request from the user’s next of kin or other proper legal request to do so. 

**  
****  

  5. 5\. How We Share Information
  
**   

**** friendsQ is about sharing information with others — friends and people in your networks — while providing you with [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/) that you can use to restrict other users from accessing your information. We share your information with third parties when we believe the sharing is permitted by you, reasonably necessary to offer our services, or when legally required to do so. For example: 

**When you make a payment.**  When you enter into transactions with others or make payments on friendsQ, we will only share transaction information with those third parties necessary to complete the transaction and will require those third parties to agree to respect the privacy of your information. 

**When you invite a friend to join.**  When you ask us to invite a friend to join friendsQ, we will send your friend a message on your behalf using your name. We may also send periodic reminders to them in your name. 

**When you choose to share your information with marketers.**  You may choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers that are not associated with friendsQ through on-site offers. This is entirely at your discretion and we will not provide your information to these marketers without your consent. 

**To help your friends find you.  **By default, we make certain information you have posted to your profile available in search results on friendsQ to help your friends find you. However, you can control who has access to this information, as well as who can find you in searches, through your [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/). We also partner with email, sms and instant messaging providers to help their users identify which of their contacts are friendsQ users, so that we can promote friendsQ to those users. 

**To give search engines access to publicly available information.**  We generally limit search engines’ access to our site. We may allow them to access information set to the “everyone” setting and your public search listing (but you can turn off your public search listing in your [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/)). 

**To help improve or promote our service.**  Sometimes we share aggregated information with third parties to help improve or promote our service. But we only do so in such a way that no individual user can be identified or linked to any specific action or information. 

**To provide you with services.**  We may provide information to service providers that help us bring you the services we offer. For example, we may use third parties to help host our website, send out email updates about friendsQ, remove repetitive information from our user lists, process payments, or provide search results or links (including sponsored links). These service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time, but when this occurs we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections to limit their use of that information to helping us provide the service. 

**To advertise our services.**  We may ask advertisers outside of friendsQ to display ads promoting our services. We may ask them to deliver those ads based on the presence of a cookie, but in doing so will not share any other information with the advertiser. 

**To offer joint services.**  We may provide services jointly with other companies. If you use these services, we may share your information to facilitate that service. However, we will identify the partner and their privacy policy will apply to you before you use that service. It is always recommended to read their privacy policy as we have no control over it. 

**To share information with third party websites.**  friendsQ is a means of sharing actions you have taken on third party sites, such as when you make a purchase or post a review, with your friends on friendsQ. In order to provide you as a friendsQ user with clear disclosure of the activity information being collected on third party sites and potentially shared with your friends on friendsQ, we collect certain information from that site and present it to you after you have completed an action on that site. Like many other websites that interact with third party sites, we may receive some information even if you are logged out from friendsQ, or that pertains to non-friendsQ users, from those sites in conjunction with the technical operation of the system. In cases where we receive information from such third party sites on users that are not logged in, or on non-friendsQ users, we do not attempt to associate it with individual friendsQ accounts and will discard it. 

**To respond to legal requests and prevent harm.**  We may disclose information pursuant to subpoenas, court orders, or other requests (including criminal and civil matters) if we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law. This may include respecting requests from jurisdictions outside of the United States where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law under the local laws in that jurisdiction, apply to users from that jurisdiction, and are consistent with generally accepted international standards. We may also share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activity, to prevent imminent bodily harm, or to protect ourselves and you from people violating our [Statement of Rights and Responsibilities](http://friendsq.com/terms/). This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts or other government entities. 

**Transfer in the Event of Sale or Change of Control.**  If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes, we may transfer your information to the new owner so that the service can continue to operate. In such a case, your information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. 

**HOW CAN YOU VIEW CHANGE OR REMOVE YOUR INFORMATION**

**Viewing and editing your profile.**  You may change or delete your profile information at any time by going to your profile page and clicking [Edit My Profile](http://friendsq.com/user/setting/). Information will be updated immediately. While you cannot delete your date of birth, you can use the setting on the info tab of your [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/), [auction settings](http://friendsq.com/auctions/settings/) and [business settings](http://friendsq.com/businesses/settings/) to hide all or part of it from other users. 

**Deleting your account.**  If you want to stop using your account you may delete it by clicking [Edit My Profile](http://friendsq.com/user/setting/). You should only delete your account if you are certain you never want to reactivate it. When you delete an account, it is permanently deleted. 

**Limitations on removal.**  Even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/), or it was copied or stored by other users. However, your name will no longer be associated with that information on friendsQ. Additionally, we may retain certain information to prevent identity theft and other misconduct even if deletion has been requested. 

**Backup copies.**  Removed and deleted information may persist in backup copies for up to 90 days, but will not be available to others. 

**Non-user contact information.**  If a user provides your email address to us, and you are not a friendsQ user but you want us to delete your address, you can do so by emailing us at [friendsq.com@gmail.com](mailto:friendsq.com@gmail.com?Subject=Non-Member%20Request%20Information%20Delete). However, that request will only apply to addresses we have at the time of the request and not to any addresses that users provide to us later. 

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

We do our best to keep your information secure, but we need your help. 

**Steps we take to keep your information secure.**  We keep your account information on a secured server behind a firewall. We also use automated and social measures to enhance security, such as analyzing account behavior for fraudulent or otherwise anomalous behavior, may limit use of site features in response to possible signs of abuse, may remove inappropriate content or links to illegal content, and may suspend or disable accounts for violations of our [Statement of Rights and Responsibilities](http://friendsq.com/terms/). 

**Risks inherent in sharing information.**  Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your information, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you share your information. We cannot guarantee that only authorized persons will view your information. We cannot ensure that information you share on friendsQ will not become publicly available. We are not responsible for third party circumvention of any [privacy settings](http://friendsq.com/user/privacy/) or security measures on friendsQ. You can reduce these risks by using common sense security practices such as choosing a strong password, using different passwords for different services, and using up to date antivirus software. 

**Report Violations.**  You should report any security violations to us by emailing us at [friendsq.com@gmail.com](mailto:friendsq.com@gmail.com?Subject=Security%20Violation). 

**OTHER TERMS**

**Consent to Collection and Processing of Data.**  By using friendsQ, you consent to having your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States or transferred to a secure database and processed outside the United States in a country where friendsQ operates. 

**Defined Terms.**  "Us," "we," "our," "Platform", "services", "friendsQ Application Platform" and "friendsQ" mean the same as they do in the [Statement of Rights and Responsibilities](http://friendsq.com/terms/). “Information” and “content” are used more generally and interchangeably here than in the [Statement of Rights and Responsibilities](http://friendsq.com/terms/) unless otherwise limited by the context. 

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at [http://friendsq.com/privacy](http://friendsq.com/policy/). We encourage you to visit this page periodically to be informed of how change in our privacy policy is protecting your information. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was created on July 19, 2014 at 12:00 am. 

By continuing to access or use friendsQ and any of its services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

**QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS**

If you have questions or suggestions or wish to contact our Privacy Officer, please email us at [friendsq.com@gmail.com](mailto:friendsq.com@gmail.com?Subject=Privacy%20Policy) or you can contact us at:
